A Finding Aid to the Organization of Independent Artists Records, circa 1970s-circa 2003, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Scrapbooks, circa 1977-2000; Series 7; Archival Resource Key; 0.7 Linear feet Box 28
  - Exhibition Scrapbook 5, 1980-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 21-24)
  - Exhibition Scrapbook, Critic's Choice, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Photographs, circa 1980s-circa 1990s; Series 8; Archival Resource Key; 0.2 Linear feet Box 28-29
  Photographs depict artwork, exhibitions, and installations. Additional exhibition photographs are found in the exhibition files.
  - Artwork, circa 1980s-circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Exhibitions, circa 1980-circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 27-29)
    Oversized material housed in Box 29, Folder 3.
  - Oversized Exhibition Photographs, from Box 28, Folder 29, circa 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 3)